articlesdir.org 2013-08-20

# Privacy Policy - Terms of use | Articlesdir.org

Google uses the [DoubleClick advertising cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx) on AdSense partner sites and certain Google services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web. You can view, edit, and manage your ads preferences associated with this cookie by accessing the [Ads Preferences Manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). In addition, you may choose to opt out of the DoubleClick cookie at any time by using [DoubleClick’s opt-out cookie](http://www.google.com/intl/en/privacy_ads.html).

## Information Collection and Use

Submit articles or find free articles. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Submit articles or find free articles. collects information from our users at several different points on our website, and may publish articles on other sites with our network.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site and is encrypted so cannot be read by any other website. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. We only use cookies for your convenience; for instance, to prevent the user from having to re-enter shopping cart information. If a user rejects the cookie, ordering functionality for the user will be affected.

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Sharing

We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. We use a credit card processing company to bill users for services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.

Third party advertising companies may also collect information about other sites you have visited in order to display appropriate advertisements on this site.

## Links

This web site may contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Submit articles or find free articles are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this web site.

## Correction/Updating Personal Information

If a user's personally identifiable information changes (such as your post code), or if a user no longer desires our service, we will endeavour to provide a way to correct, update or remove that user's personal data provided to us.

## Choice/Opt-out

If you use this site to purchase services you may occasionally receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications on our order form. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials from our partners may opt-out of receiving these communications by replying to unsubscribe in the subject line in the email, or by contacting us directly. Users of our site are notified when their information is being collected or used by any third parties. We do this so our users can make an informed choice as to whether they should proceed with services that require an third party, or not.

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we would notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected
